Your eyes are
about to pop out.
You are not losing a thing
from this situation, are you?
That's just your opinion.
I'm the type who
really depends on the teacher.
It was so tough for me back in
high school because of that.
Are you a sociopath
or something?
That's a fresh take.
I've never heard
that one before.
So, it really is
about revenge, huh?
Pretending to be friendly
to find out my weaknesses.
That's your plan, isn't it?
Why would I do that?
I've never done
anything I'd regret.
Even if I went back to the
basketball club's meeting
I'd do the same thing.
Aren't you ashamed of acting
like a big shot because you're
older and the president?
What do you mean
acting like a big shot?
Hold on a second.
You can't be serious.
Just wait a moment.
Yeah.
Are you at
the Humanities Building?
Why?
Cheol-myeong is back
at school after a long time.
It'd be awkward
if we ran into him.
That guy will find something
to nitpick about again.
Ah.
Come with me for a bit.
What?
I'll explain later
but for now...